[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Lethality: He will not stop, EVER, until you are dead. What assassin from the year 2029 AD, had you better believe when he says Ill be back.?", "correct_answer": "Terminator", "incorrect_answers": ["Predator", "Kothoga", "Replicant"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1970, Elio Fiorucci showed designer jeans for the first time in which city?", "correct_answer": "Milan", "incorrect_answers": ["Rome", "Paris", "New York"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During what war is Francis Ford Coppolas 1979 movie Apocalypse Now set?", "correct_answer": "Vietnam War", "incorrect_answers": ["Korean War", "Second World War", "Third World War"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the official language spoken in Egypt?", "correct_answer": "Arabic", "incorrect_answers": ["Arabic and French", "Arabic, English and French", "Arabic and English"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the earlier clues turns out to be the tool used to open the secret chamber in the movie National Treasure?", "correct_answer": "Pipe", "incorrect_answers": ["Glasses", "Masonic ring", "Candlestick"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the first person WALL-E comes in contact with on the Axiom?", "correct_answer": "John", "incorrect_answers": ["Mary", "Shelby Forthwright", "The Captain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Often referred to as Sasquatch, this unbelievable creature is said to be a large hairy humanoid living in the wild parts of North America.", "correct_answer": "Bigfoot", "incorrect_answers": ["Rodan", "Bogeyman", "Yeti"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "From 1984-1986, Ernest Borgnine starred with Jan-Michael Vincent as an aging helicopter pilot in which program?", "correct_answer": "Airwolf", "incorrect_answers": ["Boones Sky", "Flight Zero", "Johnny Guitar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Golgi apparatus found in most eukaryotic cells participates in the sorting and modification of what type of organic compounds?", "correct_answer": "Proteins", "incorrect_answers": ["Water molecules", "Carbohydrates", "Lipids"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these movies has not won a Razzie?", "correct_answer": "Tin Cup", "incorrect_answers": ["Wyatt Earp", "The Postman", "Robin Hood: Prince of Thieves"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many of the astronauts who have flown in space between 1959 and 2009 were from Oklahoma?", "correct_answer": "6", "incorrect_answers": ["20", "0", "3"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these doctors is qualified to treat alcohol withdrawal?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Family Practitioner", "Psychiatrist", "Internist"]}]